so i just wanted to come on here and shout out all my caribbean people and that includes the
caribbean people who are settled in south america including the guyanese and even the venezuelans
because we are watching an entire dismantling and dissolving of how to handle a dispute over there
in um israel we are seeing people just acting up so they're doing genocide they're just hitting
people shooting people beyond any type of punity but over here we are seeing people who are in a
dispute that of course was started by the british saying you know what we're not gonna have no force
we're not gonna bust up everybody we're just gonna have civil conversation and conflict resolution and
we're gonna work with the people who are also a part of the region to do so so i want to big up all
you're there doing everything you can you know we have the bayesian people there we have grenadians
larger paul spice massive we have the vincent the vincent saint vincent there and a lot of other folks
brazil involved in making sure that this is settled civilly as humanity so big up all you because this
right here is a demonstration of how one should act when a problem is afoot not out here i can just so
barbaric and such
you